{
    "subject": "resource/Dmitry_Kramkov",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralStudent",
    "object": "resource/Juan_Carlos_Rivera",
    "human_readable": "Dmitry Kramkov was a doctoral student of Juan Carlos Rivera.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884838461875916,
            "question": "Was Dmitry Kramkov a student of Juan Carlos Rivera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9724895358085632,
            "question": "What was Juan Carlos Rivera's role in Dmitry Kramkov's education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.951908528804779,
            "question": "What is the academic connection between Dmitry Kramkov and Juan Carlos Rivera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8978311419487,
            "question": "In what capacity did Juan Carlos Rivera work with Dmitry Kramkov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8510836958885193,
            "question": "Who guided Dmitry Kramkov through his doctoral studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8334761261940002,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Dmitry Kramkov and Juan Carlos Rivera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8200123906135559,
            "question": "Who was Dmitry Kramkov's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7430981397628784,
            "question": "Name the supervisor of Dmitry Kramkov's doctorate."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7363967895507812,
            "question": "To whom did Dmitry Kramkov report during his doctoral program?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4946683645248413,
            "question": "Who mentored Dmitry Kramkov during his doctoral research?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dmitry Kramkov was a doctoral student of Juan Carlos Rivera.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5988_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Dmitry Kramkov report during his doctoral program?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5988_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the supervisor of Dmitry Kramkov's doctorate.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5988_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Dmitry Kramkov's doctoral advisor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5988_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5988_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "Repeat  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Repeat**\n\nConsidering the complex mathematical problems involved in graph theory and its applications, it's unlikely that personal relationships such as a doctoral student status would have a direct impact. However, academic connections can sometimes imply shared interests or involvement in similar areas of research related to graph analysis, optimization, and visualization. Still, without further information on Dmitry Kramkov's work or pursuits within this specific context, any potential connection remains speculative and likely tangential to the primary focus on graph-related mathematical problems."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "No."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": " Dmitry Kramkov's relationship as a doctoral student of Juan Carlos Rivera during the given timeframe (2005-2006) is not directly evident from the provided data. However, without additional information about their academic backgrounds and collaboration history, it cannot be confirmed with certainty whether he was indeed a doctoral student of Juan Carlos Rivera at that time."
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "Juan Carlos Rivera"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no evidence or reference to Dmitry Kramkov as a doctoral student of Juan Carlos Rivera in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Dmitry Kramkov or Juan Carlos Rivera's relationship in the provided text.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no information about Dmitry Kramkov being a doctoral student of Juan Carlos Rivera.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not contain any information about Dmitry Kramkov being a doctoral student of Juan Carlos Rivera. The details listed are related to seminars and lectures, and do not include any academic mentorship or student-teacher relationships.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}